pcreview.co.uk 2018-12-24

# Privacy Policy | PC Review

We are PC Review ("we", "our", "us"). We’re committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. If you have questions about your personal information please contact us.

## What information we hold about you

The type of data that we collect and process includes:

  * Your name or username.
  * Your email address.
  * Your IP address.

Further data may be collected if you choose to share it, such as if you fill out fields on your profile.

We collect some or all of this information in the following cases:

  * You register as a member on this site.
  * You fill out our contact form.
  * You browse this site. See "Cookie policy" below.
  * You fill out fields on your profile.

## How your personal information is used

We may use your personal information in the following ways:

  * For the purposes of making you a registered member of our site, in order for you to contribute content to this site.
  * We may use your email address to inform you of activity on our site.
  * Your IP address is recorded when you perform certain actions on our site. Your IP address is never publicly visible.

## Other ways we may use your personal information.

In addition to notifying you of activity on our site which may be relevant to you, from time to time we may wish to communicate with all members any important information such as newsletters or announcements by email. You can opt-in to or opt-out of such emails in your profile.

We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you in the course of your interaction with our site. This information may include technical information about the browser or type of device you're using. This information will be used purely for the purposes of analytics and tracking the number of visitors to our site.

## Keeping your data secure

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to us is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable measures and procedures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect.

## Cookie policy

Cookies are small text files which are set by us on your computer which allow us to provide certain functionality on our site, such as being able to log in, or remembering certain preferences.

We have a detailed cookie policy and more information about the cookies that we set on this page.

## Rights

You have a right to access the personal data we hold about you or obtain a copy of it. To do so please contact us. If you believe that the information we hold for you is incomplete or inaccurate, you may contact us to ask us to complete or correct that information.

You also have the right to request the erasure of your personal data. Please contact us if you would like us to remove your personal data.

## Acceptance of this policy

Continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of this policy. If you do not accept the policy then please do not use this site. When registering we will further request your explicit acceptance of the privacy policy.

## Changes to this policy

We may make changes to this policy at any time. You may be asked to review and re-accept the information in this policy if it changes in the future.

## Advertiser Information

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL: [ http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

You may opt-out of receiving some advertising cookies by visiting [ http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

We use Skimlinks for processing affiliate links on our site. You will receive notification of this when clicking through via one of these links. You may opt-out of Skimlinks cookies by visiting this page: [https://optout.skimlinks.com](https://optout.skimlinks.com/)

Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their privacy policy or contact their data protection officer via privacy@exponential.com.
